buzzworthy.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy

Because your privacy is important to us, BUZZWORTHY has established procedures to protect any personal information you provide to us in accordance with the following principles:

#### A. Collecting and Sharing Personal Information:

We explicitly ask when we need information that personally identifies you (“Personal Information”). For example, BUZZWORTHY asks you for your name and e-mail address if you wish to join our mailing list, and we also may request that you provide Personal Information as part of a contest, promotion, program, or service. We may also ask for other information from time to time, such as gender and date of birth, the disclosure of which will be optional. We use your Personal Information for various purposes consistent with US law, and we may occasionally inform you of new features, services, and products. We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our sites, such as the type of browser you are using, the operating system you are using, and the domain name of your internet service provider. We may use this non-personally identifiable information to improve our site and to enable us to personalize your experience on BUZZWORTHY. We may also use this information in the aggregate to analyze the BUZZWORTHY site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. BUZZWORTHY does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13).

#### B. “Cookies”:

We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable the BUZZWORTHY to relate your use of BUZZWORTHY to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided to BUZZWORTHY.

#### C. Disclosure of Information:

BUZZWORTHY reserves the right to release current or past member information in the event BUZZWORTHY believes that the membership is being or has been used in violation of the Terms of Service or other published guidelines or to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, or otherwise requested through legal process. BUZZWORTHY cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. By agreeing to the conditions of this Privacy Policy and BUZZWORTHY’s Terms of Service, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any third party when BUZZWORTHY, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate. In the event your Personal Information is being sold, rented, and/or shared with any third party we will use good faith efforts to post a notice on the site clearly stating that the information is being so used and/or give you the opportunity to opt-in to authorize the use.

#### D. Consent:

By using this website and the services available to you on our site, you consent to our collection and use of your information as described above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always aware of our policies.

#### E. Links:

We may provide links to a number of other sites that we believe can offer you useful information and services. However, we are not responsible for the privacy policies of or any actions of any third parties that control the activities of such third party sites. We suggest contacting the relevant parties controlling these sites or accessing their online policies for the relevant information about their data collection.

#### F. General Information:

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, that information can be collected and used by others. Therefore, when you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and for any other personal information.

If at any time you believe BUZZWORTHY has not adhered to these principles, please notify us via the contact us link.

#### G. Third Party Tracking and Links to Other Websites or Services:

Our websites and services include third-party advertising. These third-parties, or other third-parties that work on their behalf, may send (or “serve”) the advertisements that appear on our websites or services. These third-parties automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These third-parties may also use cookies, Javascript, Pixel Tags and other technologies to determine how long visits last and other associated information, deliver advertisements, and to collect personal information. We do not control how these advertisers collect personal information. Visitors to our websites or services should check the Privacy Policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it collects personal information. These companies may not recognize or respond to DNT headers from web browsers. Some third-parties allow you to opt-out of, or customize your preferences regarding, third-party advertisements and services. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Specifically, our websites and services make use of Google’s “Google Analytics” platform in order to collect data about where traffic to our websites and services originates, how long visits last, and other associated information. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit Google’s official Google Analytics webpage here. We have implemented a number of Google Analytics “Display Advertising” features on our websites and services, including “Remarketing,” “Google Display Network Impression Reporting,” the “DoubleClick Campaign Manager” integration, and “Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.” You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Networks ads here. Google also offers other opt-outs for Google Analytics here. Alternatively, you can opt-out of the collection of data by Google and certain other advertising service providers at the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page, [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Please note that our websites and services contain links to other websites or services that will not follow this Privacy Policy. For instance, clicking on an advertisement or on links or other elements on our websites or services may take you to an entirely different website or service. Links to other websites or services may use our logos or styles as a result of a co-branding agreement. These websites or services may independently send their own cookies to you and may collect data and make use of that data not in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other websites or services. You should check the applicable privacy policy to determine how other websites or services will handle personal information or any other data collected from or provided by you.
